One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Wealth, fame, power...
Zenginlik, şöhret, güç...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, obtained everything the world has to offer.
Dünyanın sunabileceği her şeyi elde eden adam, Korsanlar Kralı, Gold Roger.
What he said in his final moments drove countless souls to the seas.
Son sözleri dünyanın her yerinden maceracıları denize çekti.
You want my treasure?
Hazinem mi?
Go ahead.
İstiyorsanız, alabilirsiniz.
Find it!
Arayıp bulun!
Everything is right where I left it!
Bu dünyanın sunabileceği her şeyi orada bıraktım!
People set their sights on the Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams.
Artık herkes, hayallerinin peşinde Grand Line'a yelken açıyor!
The world has truly entered the Great Pirate Era!
Dünya, Büyük Korsan Çağı'na girdi!
"Oden's Travel Record"
"Oden'in Seyir Defteri"
D?
D. mi?
I never thought I'd be able to meet you!
Bir gün seninle tanışacağım hiç aklıma gelmezdi.
"O-Oden"...
"O-Oden"...
Is that my father's journal?!
Babamın defteri mi o?
Straw Hat Luffy
Hasır Şapkalı Luffy
It contains every detail about his grand life and the world he experienced!
Dolu dolu yaşantısı ve dünyayı keşfinin tüm ayrıntıları bu defterde yer alıyor.
On that day, I found it at the river below Oden Castle.
Malum gün, bunu Oden Kalesi'nin oradaki nehirden aldım.
Someone in the castle must have kept it from burning...
Biri bunu yangından kurtarmış.
Lord Oden's...
Oden-sama'nın...
Momonosuke!
Momonosuke-kun!
He wrote a lot about you as well.
Seninle ilgili de birçok şey yazıyor.
You were born on Whitebeard's ship, right?!
Beyazsakal'ın gemisinde doğmuşsun!
And then you went on to Roger's ship!
Sonra da Roger'ın gemisine gitmişsin.
Mm-hmm.
Hıhı.
Th-Though, since I was so young, I do not remember much...
Ama çok küçük olduğumdan hiç hatırlamıyorum.
Whitebeard, Roger, and Oden...
Beyazsakal, Roger ve Oden.
They all said...
Ortak bir şey söylediler...
that twenty years in the future,
"Bundan en az 20 yıl sonra...
the New World was sure to be overrun by young and powerful pirates!
genç ve güçlü korsanlar birbiri ardına Yeni Dünya'ya gelecek."
That future is now!
O vakit geldi!
I was sure that Ace would be among them, leading the pack...
Onların başının da Ace olacağına inanıyordum.
But when he died, I remembered something from that night!
Ama o öldüğünde bir şeyi hatırladım. O gece dediği bir şeyi!
What...?
Ne...?
Crap!
Hass...
I let it slip!
Ağzımdan kaçırdım!
I wasn't supposed to say that!
Yanlışlıkla söyledim.
You didn't hear that! Forget about it!
Bunu demedim sayalım!
And don't you dare laugh either!
Bak gülme,
Sabo and I won't stand for it!
Sabo'yla ben çok kızarız.
That's at the end...
Kardeşimin hayali bu.
Sure, we laughed when Luffy told us, but that's okay!
Luffy bunu dediğinde Sabo'yla gülmüştük.
We're the only ones who are allowed to laugh...
Ama başkasının gülmesine izin vermeyiz.
'cause we believe in him!
Ona inanıyoruz çünkü.
We really think he can do it, so–
Onda bu potansiyel var, bu yüzden–
Ace!
Ace!
Huh?
Ha?
Hey!
Hey!
What's wrong, Yamato?
Neyin var, Yamato?
I won't laugh!
Ben gülmeyeceğim.
Those were the Pirate King's exact words!
Korsanlar Kralı da aynısını demişti!
The very words that stunned Oden!
Oden de çok etkilenmişti!
In Kozuki Oden's journal, there was a great man who said the same thing!
Yolculuğu sırasında Kozuki Oden de aynısını diyen büyük bir adam görmüş.
I'd never laugh at that!
Hayatta gülmem!
Your brother is incredible!
Kardeşin inanılmaz biri!
A great man, huh?
Büyük adam ha?
Good to hear!
İyiymiş.
Maybe Luffy and I can grab a drink with him someday!
Luffy'yle beraber bir gün onunla içeriz umarım.
I'm sure you guys would get along!
Aranızdan su sızmazdı kesin.
But he's already dead.
Çoktan ölmeseydi.
He is?!
Öldü mü?
Well, in that case, it'd be hard to see him...
Yazık oldu. Kadeh tokuşturamayacağız.
It's done!
Bitirdim.
Oh?
Oh?
This is your vivre card!
Bu senin vivre kartın.
This is it?
Bu muymuş?
It's just some paper.
Bildiğin kağıt parçası bu ya.
Yeah! But this piece of paper will bring us together again one day!
Evet, bu kağıt parçası bizi tekrar bir araya getirecek.
Give a piece to anyone you want to keep track of or meet again.
Ayrılmak istemediğin ya da tekrar görmek istediğin birine bundan bir parça ver.
Okay!
Anladım!
I'll be sure to do that.
Öyle yaparım.
Ace!
Ace!
Yamato?!
Yamato?!
We will meet again one day!
Tekrar görüşelim...
Ace!
Ace!
You bet!
Elbette!
In reality...
Ama...
that would be our final meeting.
bu onu son görüşümdü.
I had no idea what was happening in the outside world that day,
O gün dış dünyada neler olup bittiğini bilmesem de...
but I read about it in the newspaper later.
olanları daha sonra gazeteden okudum.
I learned that Ace was the son of the Pirate King, Gol D. Roger...
Ace'in Korsanlar Kralı Gol D. Roger'ın oğlu olduğunu...
and that his younger brother had really made a name for himself!
ve kardeşinin cidden korsan olup nam yaptığını öğrendim.
That was the man you brought...
Kardeşi senin buraya getirdiğin Luffy!
Momonosuke.
Momonosuke-kun.
I return this to you, of course.
Hakkın olarak bunu sana veriyorum.
This is what Oden wrote about the future...
Oden'in gelecek ile ilgili kaleme aldıkları bunlar...
Twenty years from now,
Bundan en az 20 yıl sonra...
a group of young and powerful pirates shall start a new era in the New World!
gelecek çağa öncülük edecek genç ve güçlü korsanlar, birbiri ardına Yeni Dünya'ya gelecek.
If I die before then...
Şayet ölürsem...
they will be the ones...
Kaido'yu...
to strike down Kaido!
onlar devirecek!
And here's another one...
Biri daha geldi.
How about you sit back and watch how it's done?!
Siz oturun, ben hallederim.
I refuse!
Reddediyorum.
Same here!
Ben de.
So many heads ripe for the taking!
Kellesini almalık ne çok kişi geldi.
Straw Hat...
Hasır Şapka.
Linlin!
Linlin!
You wanna guess what this brat said he'd be, right to my face?!
Bil bakalım bu velet karşıma geçip ne olacağım demiştir.
He sure is a cheeky one...
Küstahın teki.
He talked a big game to me too!
Bana da haddini aşan sözler söyledi.
He even destroyed my castle!
Kalemi de yerle bir etti.
I believe you owe me an apology, Straw Hat!
Önce özür dile, Hasır Şapka.
Hey, punk...
Lan velet.
Tell us again what you said you'll be...
Karşımızdayken...
Say it right to our faces!
ne olacaksın bir daha söyle hele!
You alright, Kin'emon?
İyi misin, Kin'emon?
I'm sorry...
Özür dilerim.
I took too long.
Geç kaldım.
I am... chagrined...
P... Perişanım.
A-Alas...
Öteki...
when I pass on...
dünyada...
I will have nothing to show Lord Oden but my shame!
efendime bakacak yüzüm... yok!
Kin'e–
Kin'e–
Would you carry...
Wano'ya...
Wano upon your back?!
sahip çıkar mısın?
I beg–
Ya–
Dummy!
Aptal!
Of course I will!
Elbette çıkarım!
It's my friends' country!
Burası dostlarımın ülkesi!
Hey, brat!
Lan velet.
Sir...
Luffy-dono...
We are all in...
minnettarım.
Traffy!
Trao!
Send all of them downstairs!
Hepsini aşağıya yolla!
Why is it shaking again?!
Yine ne sarsıntısı bu?
Luffy...
Luffy...
You call it haki, but in Wano we refer to it as ryuo.
Sizin haki dediğiniz şey Wano'da ryuo olarak biliniyor.
It means "to flow."
"Akış" anlamına geliyor.
Lord Oden was executed!
Oden-sama idam edildi!
By the shogun of Wano and the pirate Kaido!
Wano şogunu tarafından, korsan Kaido'nun da yardımıyla...
Sir Raizo is safe!
Raizo-dono güvende!
We'd never sell out our friends!
Ölürüz de dostlarımızı satmayız!
We'd never sell out our friends! Listen! You-gara must press on!
Ölürüz de dostlarımızı satmayız! Dinleyin! Siz-gara ilerlemeye devam etmelisiniz!
Listen! You-gara must press on!
Dinleyin! Siz-gara ilerlemeye devam etmelisiniz!
The neighborly man of Ebisu Town is heading off to the great beyond!
Ebisu Kasabası'nın neşeli adamı öteki dünyaya geçmek üzere!
The fires of rebellion... Do they continue to burn?!
Ebisu Kasabası'nın neşeli adamı öteki dünyaya geçmek üzere!
All ships, to Onigashima!
Tüm gemiler, Onigashima'ya!
Charge!
İleri!
On the day Kaido killed Oden twenty years ago...
20 yıl önce Oden, Kaido tarafından öldürüldüğünde...
this country stopped moving forward!
bu ülke duraklama çağına girmedi mi?
No one deserves to be laughed at when they die.
Kimse ölürken gülünmeyi hak etmez.
What's wrong with a stranger defending this land?!
Yabancıyım diye ülkeyi kurtaramaz mıyım?
You say it! Aren't you an important person?!
Konuşsana! Önemli biri değil miydin?!
You're the leader of these great men, aren't you?!
Bu harika insanların lideri değil misin?!
I want to defeat Kaido!
Kaido'yu devirmek istiyorum!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Red...
Kızıl...
Roc!
Kaya!
Hey, Kaido! What are you doing?!
Hey, Kaido! Ne yapıyorsun?!
How the hell did he knock you down?!
Sen yere düşmezsin!
I'm Monkey D. Luffy.
Ben, Monkey D. Luffy.
The man who's gonna surpass you both...
Sizi geride bırakacak...
and become the King of the Pirates!
ve Korsanlar Kralı olacağım!